recruitmentvoice.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy - Recruitmentvoice

Privacy Policy , The privacy of our visitors is of main importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.recruitmentvoice.com and how it is used. The privacy policy document here we afford for intimating you about how we work on our job portal. This portal reflects the information collected from various websites. So, when one who is applying for a job or about to attend any walkin, based on the information provided in our portal is requested to verify the same from various other sites or from the official website. We don’t assure that the data provided here is completely correct. One can use the information at their own risk. We are not responsible for any consequences that occur on applying for any job or walkin data that we provided in our portal.

www.recruitmentvoice.com is website created as a resource to help people know about latest recruitment, exams and results, answer key, admit cad etc. The site primarily focused on Government jobs, bank jobs, railway jobs, defence jobs, private jobs, exam results, exam admit card, answer keys, interview, previous question papers, exam syllabus, admissions, entrance exams and more. It intends to be a great platform for job seekers without getting involved in legal suits. So, here is the disclaimer policy for www.recruitmentvoice.com, Utmost care is generally taken while we are publishing the information in our portal. Our source of collecting information is completely from other websites. There might be some mistakes in our portal which are made unknowingly because the effort is made completely by humans.

Click any link at your own risk in our portal. We are not responsible for any loss you get on doing so. We don’t have control on the portal as these are maintained by third party people. The Job seekers are advised to be careful and check the information from other websites and make conform regarding any particular advertisement.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at pradeepreddy544@gmail.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.recruitmentvoice,com and how it is used.

Logos that we use in our portal are completely collected from other websites and sometimes from the official website. We provide it for more interactive to the topic that we are providing in our portal. There is no other intention in providing the logos. Owners of the logo, please write to us if you feel that we are violating the copy write of your logo. We assure you that the logo will be removed in short span of time.
